# ALEKSANDR JASIN, MA MARKETING

+ 353 86 083 6926, 5 Shackleton Glen, Shackleton park, Lucan, Co Dublin aleksandr.jasin@gmail.com



Aleksandr Jasin



linkedin.com/in/Aleksandrjasin



Aleksandr Jasin

# About Me:

Marketing Professional with BSc in Business Administration, MA in Marketing and passion for everything related to marketing, customer service and sales. With overall experience of more than 8 years in the hospitality industry and over 10 year in providing excellent customer service, I was able gain expertise and knowledge needed to become a skilled team manager at the present.

# Work Experience:

# CS EMEA Customer Experience Lead, G8

Airbnb

(www.airbnb.com)

09/2017 - Present

As a CS EMEA Customer Experience Lead my main objective were as follows:

- Leading Innovation and product testing team of 15 Customer Service Managers in EMEA by setting innovation strategy and defining how success looks like.
- Making sure the team is provided with an innovation framework i.e. processes and enabling tools.
- Innovating by example fostering brainstorming sessions, feedback floating, enabling decision making within the team.
- Communicating, inspiring and diffusing making sure communication within the team and other stakeholders is clear and concise. Setting processes to success by handling the noise and avoiding disruptions.
- Ensuring Team members are set for success with their day to day activities, supporting their career progression. Making sure the team feels comfortable to provide constructive feedback to each other and to their manager. Maintaining strong emphasis on the performance piece - making sure the team is adherent to the set targets. Analysing the trends in metric fluctuations and identifying opportunities for upskilling within the team. Defining KPIs for the team.
- I have a highly motivated team that delivers strong consistent results and their customers are loyal followers of our brand. This is achieved by focusing their efforts in 3 main areas:
- 1. Creating Strong Employee Engagement.
- 2. Performance Accountability (NPS, SPD, AUX state adherence, SLA, FTR, FCR, AHT, Occupancy, Shrinkage).

3. Translating Strategy into Action/Solving Problems.

# Team Coordinator/ Regional Support Coordinator, G6

AirBnB

(www.airbnb.com)

05/2014-09/2017

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- First point of contact for the specialists
- Providing full support to the TL
- Monitoring Inboxes, SLAs and Phone Lines in real time
- Coming up with daily plans to tackle inboxes and saving SLA
- Running 1:1 with specialists
- Helping TL with all the metrics related to team's performance
- Updating 1:1 files, entering exceptions, advising on PTO requests from crewbies
- Triaging & Assigning: SOS, Founder aliases, urgent Social, Handoffs, Geos & PR, etc.
- Supervisor Calls: difficult cases & users
- Ticket Consults: knowledge sharing
- MGR: Four Eyes Consults & monitoring performance Vs goals
- Quality: QA reviews & Lead input to coaching requirements
- Team: Supporting new hire ramp up & team integration
- Data: Supporting Lead in monitoring key performance reports for the team, identifying areas for improvement & input to MBR
- Leadership: Coverage for Lead for PTO and stepping up to interim Lead roles
- Personal Development: Taking on projects, being gurus of specific areas e.g. bugs or doing courses or assignments
- SM escalations process revamp through close work with BPI and PartM

### Work Flow Lead For Google Adwords Russia Arvato Finance

Arvato Finance (www.arvato.ie) 11/2013 – 05/2014

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- Search and Display network advertising campaigns set up and optimization via phone, email and/or live chat.
- Meeting weekly targets against KPI (CSAT, productivity and quality).
- Communicate, support and implement new processes or policies as required by the business.
- Analysing potential traffic to estimate CPC/CPM and budget.
- Evaluating customer satisfaction and improving agents' performance.
- Daily collaboration with service specialists, engineers and Management to implement creative ways to improve our client relationships and increase revenue.
- Resolving billing and payment queries.
- Understanding customer requirements / changing demands.

#### **Key Achievements:**

- Performing over 95% weekly CSAT on average
- Proactively meeting all the KPI metrics

### **Events Manager**

The Clarence Hotel www.theclarence.ie 04/2012-05/2013

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- Copywriting advertising campaigns.
- Researching markets to identify new opportunities for events.
- Planning new promotions and initiatives, and contributing to business development.
- Communicating with clients to ascertain their precise event requirements.
- Using "Aro Connect" software for generating extensive email marketing campaigns.
- Extensive use of social media Facebook, Top Table, Menu Pages, Hotel's Website to promote hotels vision, special offers and events.
- Use of Photoshop in order to produce creative brochures, special offers.
- Generating detailed proposals for events (e.g. timelines, venues, suppliers, legal obligations, staffing and budgets).
- Budgeting and establishing financial targets and forecasts.
- Working with Fidelio booking engine.
- Coordinating venue management, caterers, stand designers, contractors and equipment hire.
- Organizing facilities for car parking, traffic control, security, first aid, hospitality and the media.
- Identifying speakers or special guests.
- Planning room layouts.
- Coordinating staffing requirements and staff briefings.
- Selling sponsorship/stand/exhibition space to potential exhibitors/partners.
- Liaising with marketing and PR colleagues to promote events.
- Coordinating suppliers, handling client queries and troubleshooting on the day of the event to ensure that all runs smoothly.
- Planning and organizing weddings of up to 135 attendees.

#### **Key Achievements:**

- Creating & implementing hotels advertisement campaigns on a regular basis.
- Fostering level of Events at the hotel through extensive use of advertisement, social media promotions, meetings with potential clients, creative marketing campaigns, email marketing.
- Creating Clarence hotel accounts on www.opentable.com and www.menupages.ie.
- Purchasing Aro Connect software for running email marketing campaigns.
- Building an audience through hotels' Facebook account.
- My activities were the cause of the Food & Beverage department breaking even in the first quarter of 2013 (very quiet business period in hospitality).

# **Education:**

2010 – 2012 MA, Marketing

Liverpool John Moores University
Dissertation: The reasons behind service sabotage behaviour in
Hospitality industry. Prevention methods analysis.

### 2004-2009 BSc Hons, Business Administration

LCC International University, Lithuania Final Examination result: 89%.

# Additional Skills:

### Languages:

- English (Fluent)
- Russian (Native)
- Lithuanian (Fluent)

### **Software packages:**

- Google Ad Words
- Google Documents
- MS Office
- Adobe Photoshop
- Aro Connect
- Navision
- Fleetmatics

# Additional Information:

I am passionate about everything that relates to marketing, especially in creating, implementing and sustaining effective marketing campaigns. Enjoy using new technologies and software. Creative and enthusiastic about new things and experience. Strong team player but am able to work on my own as effectively as required.

References Available on Request